Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of Labor Movement Serials WAG.345
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Labor unions and organizations, 1891-2012; 188.25 Linear Feet in 24 record cartons and 139 oversize flat boxes
  - Subseries I.L: Transportation Workers, 1938-2012; 23 Linear Feet in 2 record cartons and 18 oversize flat boxes
    - Souvenir Journal: United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America (UAW) - Local 259, New York, NY, 1976 (Box 123, Folder 91)
    - Dept. Store Employee: United Department Store Employees Union - United Retail Wholesale and Dept. Store Employees of America-CIO, 1942 (Box 123, Folder 92)
    - Hard Times: United National Caucus Unemployed Committee, Washington, DC, 1975 (Box 123, Folder 93)
    - United National Caucus: United National Caucus, UAW, Detroit, MI, 1970, 1972-1973 (Box 131, Folder 2)
    - United to Win: United Taxicab Workers/Communications Workers of America, Local 9411, San Francisco, CA, 1994 (Box 123, Folder 94)
    - District Bulletin: UWO affiliate, circa 1970s (Box 172, Folder 42)
    - Voice of Rank & File in Transportation: Voice of Rank & File in Transportation, New York, NY, 1985-1992 (Box 123, Folder 95)
    - Grapevine: Voice of So. Cal. Teamsters for a Democratic Union- Local 572, Lynwood, CA, 1980 (Box 118, Folder 10)
    - Voice of the Rank & File in Transportation: Voice of the Rank & File in Transportation, New York, NY, circa 1980s (Box 123, Folder 96)
    - Warehouse Workers: Warehouse Employees Local Union, 1936 (Box 131, Folder 4)
    - Bombardier: Willow Run Bomber Local 50, Detroit, MI, 1944-1945 (Box 131, Folder 5-6)
    - Wisconsin Teamster: Wisconsin Teamsters, Inc./Wisconsin Teamsters Joint Council No. 39, Milwaukee, WI, 1986 (Box 123, Folder 97)
    - 692 Newsletter, 1980 (Box 123, Folder 98)
    - Hot Cargo, 1992 (Box 123, Folder 99)
    - Northwest Passage: Seattle, WA, 1970-1986 (Box 131, Folder 7-8, Box 132, Folder 1-5)
    - Railroading: Alliance, NE, 1993 (Box 123, Folder 101)
    - Transport Bulletin (Taxi Edition), 1937-1940 (Box 83, Folder 11)
- Series II: Labor Law, 1945-2007; 3.25 Linear Feet in 2 record cartons, 1 manuscript box, and 1 oversize flat box
  This series collects various serials and publications relevant to labor law and legislation. Topics include the development and introduction of Occupational Safety and Health legislation (often through regional organizations like Chicago's CACOSH or Connecticut's ConnectiCOSH); efforts to raise the minimum wage (Ad Hoc Committee for Workers' Compensation; National Unemployed Network; UNITE); and general trade commentary on jobs and employment (Daily Labor Report; publications by the National Labor Law Center).
  - Workers' Compensation Update: Ad Hoc Committee for Workers' Compensation, New York, NY, 1985 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Arbitration in the Schools: American Arbitration Association, New York, NY, 1995 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - Labor News: Amnesty International of the USA, San Francisco, CA, 1979 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Legislative Brief: Associated Industries of New York State, Inc., Albany, NY, 1977 (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - What's New in Collective Bargaining Negotiations & Contracts: Bureau of National Affairs, 1976 (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Daily Labor Report: Bureau of National Affairs, Inc., Washington, DC, 1955, 1995 (Box 96, Folder 1-20)
  - Personnel Policies Forum: Bureau of National Affairs, Inc., Washington, DC, 1965 (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - Retail Services Labor Report: Bureau of National Affairs, Inc., Washington, DC, 1978 (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - Service Industries Labor Report: Bureau of National Affairs, Inc., Washington, DC, 1955 (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - Union Labor Report's On The Line: A Guide for Union Stewards: Bureau of National Affairs, Inc., Washington, DC, 1983, 1988, 1989, 1993 (Box 172, Folder 47)
  - CACOSH: Chicago Area Committee on Occupational Safety & Health, Chicago, IL, 1975-1980 (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Child Labor Monitor: Child Labor Coalition, Washington, DC, 1994-1997 (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - What is ConnectiCOSH: ConnectiCOSH, CT, circa 1970s (Box 95, Folder 10)
  - ECOSH News: Electronics Committee on Safety and Health, Mountain View, CA, 1978-1979 (Box 95, Folder 11)
  - Grapevine: Grassroots Organizers in the Chicago-Calumet Region, New York, NY, 1982 (Box 162, Folder 25)
  - Safety First: Greater New York Safety Council, Brookfield, WI, 1997 (Box 95, Folder 12)
  - Hazards: Hazards Publications Ltd., Chicago, IL, 1994-1999, 2006-2007 (Box 162, Folder 22)
  - LLR: Legal-Legislative Reporter news Bulletin: International Foundation of Employee Benefit Plans, Milwaukee, WI, 1988 (Box 95, Folder 13)
  - Highlights from April 4th, 2001 National Student Labor Day of Action: Jobs with Justice, New Brunswick, NJ (Box 162, Folder 16)
  - A Call to Come to a National Congress of the Unemployed: JOIN, Chicago, IL, 1983 (Box 95, Folder 14)
  - La Verdad / The Truth: La Verdad, Berkeley, CA, 1979 (Box 95, Folder 15)
  - Comparative International Industrial Relations: Labor Law Journal, Chicago, IL, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 16)
  - LOHOP Catalog: Labor Occupational Health Program, New York, NY, 1991 (Box 95, Folder 17)
  - Speak Out for Safety & Health: Maryland Committee on Occupational Safety & Health (MaryCOSH), New York, NY, 1979, 1981 (Box 172, Folder 71)
  - Lump-Sum City Newsletter: Massachusetts Organization of Disabled Workers, Washington, DC, 1981 (Box 95, Folder 18)
  - Occupational Health Project: Medical Committee for Human Rights, Washington, DC, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 19)
  - Changing Years: National Child Labor Committee, Washington, DC, 1954 (Box 95, Folder 20)
  - National Civic Federation Review: National Civic Federation, Washington, DC, 1906-1911 (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Jobs Impact Bulletin: National Committee for Full Employment, Washington, DC, 1985-1988 (Box 95, Folder 21)
  - Report to the Nation: National Council for a Permanent FEPC, Washington, DC, 1945 (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - NIOSH Alert: National Institute for Occupational Safety and Health, Washington, DC, 1995 (Box 95, Folder 22)
  - National Labor Law Center Shopsheets: National Labor Law Center, Washington, DC, 1982 (Box 95, Folder 23)
  - Plant Closings & Runaway Industries: Strategies for Labor: National Labor Law Center/National Lawyers Guild, McKeesport, PA, 1981 (Box 95, Folder 24)
  - Right to Work National Newsletter: National Right to Work Committee, 1956 (Box 95, Folder 25)
  - Healthy Office Report: National Safe Workplace Institute, Linden, NJ, 1991 (Box 95, Folder 26)
  - National Unemployed News: National Unemployed Network, New York, NY, 1983-1984 (Box 95, Folder 27)
  - Reconversion: New Century Publishers, New York, NY, 1945 (Box 95, Folder 28)
  - News: New Jersey Committee for Occupational Safety and Health (NJCOSH), New York, NY, 1980 (Box 95, Folder 29)
  - Newsletter: New York Committee for Occupational Safety and Health, Albany, NY, 1984 (Box 95, Folder 30)
  - NYCOSH Bi-Weekly: New York Committee for Occupational Safety and Health, Inc., Durham, NC, 1997-1998 (Box 95, Folder 31)
  - Newsletter: New York Labor-Management Council of Health and Welfare Plans, Inc., 1971 (Box 172, Folder 46)
  - HELP-NJ Update: NJ Right to Know & Act Coalition, 1990 (Box 95, Folder 32)
  - NCOSH Safety & Health News: North Carolina Occupational Safety and Health Project (NCOSH), Philadelphia, PA, 1980-1984 (Box 95, Folder 33)
  - Copy Right: NYSUT United Teachers, Providence, RI, 1980 (Box 163, Folder 48)
  - OEDA Newsletter: Occupational and Environmental Diseases Association, Madison, WI, 1998-1999 (Box 95, Folder 34)
  - Working Together: Ontario Ministry of Labour, San Francisco, CA, 1982 (Box 95, Folder 35)
  - Get Organized! Seize The Time In '77 - Build A National Workers Organization: Organizing Committee for a National Workers Organization, San Francisco, CA, 1977 (Box 162, Folder 26)
  - Safer Times: Philadelphia Area Project on Occupational Safety and Health (PHILAPOSH), Nashville, TN, 1977-1984 (Box 95, Folder 36)
  - Are You Concerned About Health & Safety on the Job: Tennessee Committee on Occupational Safety and Health (TNCOSH), circa 1970s (Box 95, Folder 37)
  - Minimum Wage Revisited: UNITE, Milwaukee, WI, 1995 (Box 163, Folder 46)
  - Labor Law and Practice in Spain: United States Department of Labor Bureau of Labor Statistics, Milwaukee, WI, 1965 (Box 163, Folder 43)
  - Labor Law and Practice in Turkey: United States Department of Labor, Bureau of Labor Statistics, Milwaukee, WI, 1963 (Box 163, Folder 42)
  - Proceedings: Workers Defense League, New York, NY, 1969 (Box 163, Folder 35)
  - WYNCOSH: Western New York Council on Occupational Safety and Health, circa 1970s (Box 163, Folder 26)
  - Health & Safety News: Wisconsin Committee on Occupational Safety & Health, 1988 - 1989 (Box 163, Folder 5)
  - WISCOSH: Wisconsin Committee on Occupational Safety and Health, Sheffield, England, 1979 (Box 95, Folder 51)
- Series III: Labor News, 1897-2002; 7.25 Linear Feet in 1 record carton and 5 oversize flat boxes
  This series contains a range of daily and weekly labor newspapers, journals, trade magazines, and other publications, often chronicling labor activity -- unionization, collective bargaining, plant closings -- at the regional level, for example Denver, Colorado's Rocky Mountain Workers' Voice; Miami's Union Record of Florida; and Pennsylvania's Mon Valley Update.
  - Redwood Empire Labor Journal: All American Federation of Labor Unions in Northwestern California, Eureka, CA, 1953 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - American Co-Operative News: American Co-Operative News, Cambridge, MA, 1897 (Box 163, Folder 2)
  - Conspiracy in Coal: Appalachian Movement Press, Huntington, WV, circa 1970s (Box 163, Folder 3)
  - Harlan & Bell Kentucky 1931-2 - National Miner's Union: Appalachian Movement Press, Huntington, WV, 1972 (Box 172, Folder 48)
  - When Southern Labor Stirs: Appalachian Movement Press, Huntington, WV, 1972 (Box 163, Folder 4)
  - Wage Earner: Association of Catholic Trade Unionists, Detroit, MI, 1945 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Wildcat: Black & Red, Detroit, MI, 1974 (Box 163, Folder 6)
  - Black Hawk Labor News: Black Hawk Union AFL-CIO / Hawkeye Area Labor Council, AFL-CIO, Cedar Falls, IO, 1954 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Black Lung Bulletin: Black Lung Association, Charleston, WV, 1971 (Box 163, Folder 7)
  - Newsletter: Bridge & Tunnel Officers Benevolent Association, 1984 (Box 163, Folder 8)
  - Monthly Labor Review: Bureau of Labor Statistics, 1939 (Box 163, Folder 47)
  - Inside Labor Relations: Business Research Publications, Washington, DC, 1995 (Box 163, Folder 9)
  - Job Safety Consultant: Business Research Publications, Inc., New York, NY, 1985 (Box 163, Folder 10)
  - White Collar Management: Business Research Publications, Inc., New York, NY, 1979 (Box 163, Folder 11)
  - Union Plus: Better Living for Union Members and Their Families: Cadmus Custom Publishing, Boston, MA, 1995 (Box 163, Folder 12-13)
  - Working Papers in Labor Studies: Center for Labor Studies, Seattle, WA, 1997 (Box 163, Folder 14)
  - Central Trades News: Central Trades & Labor Council of Nassau-Suffolk Counties, Hicksville, NY, 1958 (Box 164, Folder 1)
  - Wages and the Working Day: Charles H. Kerr & Company, Chicago, IL, 1946 (Box 163, Folder 15)
  - Labor World: Chattanooga Central Labor Union, Chattanooga, TN, 1946 (Box 164, Folder 2-6)
  - UWOC News: Dayton Unemployed Workers Organizing Committee, Dayton, OH, 1972 (Box 163, Folder 16)
  - Wage Rates and Hours of Labour in Canada: Department of Labour, Ottawa, Ontario, Canada, 1943 (Box 163, Folder 17)
  - Employment Trends: Division of Employment, New York, NY, 1970 (Box 163, Folder 18)
  - Employment News: Employment News, Inc., Columbus, OH, 1993 (Box 163, Folder 19)
  - No More Jobs: Employment Project, New York, NY, 2002 (Box 163, Folder 20)
  - Federated Press Central Bureau: Federated Press, Detroit, MI, 1932 (Box 166, Folder 4)
  - Federated Press Eastern Bureau: Federated Press, New York, NY, 1952 (Box 166, Folder 5-7)
  - Federated Press Special AFL Convention Service: Federated Press, 1953 (Box 166, Folder 8)
  - Federated Press Special CIO Convention Service: Federated Press, 1952 (Box 166, Folder 9)
  - Federated Press Special Labor Day Service Annual Review: Federated Press, 1953 (Box 166, Folder 10)
  - Federated Press Washington Bureau: Federated Press, Washington, DC, 1952 (Box 167, Folder 1-2)
  - Florida Labor Advocate: Florida Labor Advocate, Tampa, FL, 1954 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Labor Herald: Herald Cooperative Press, Baltimore, MD, 1942-1976 (Box 149, Folder 18, Box 175, Folder 1-7)
  - Working Paper Series: Industrial Relations Center, Minneapolis, MN, 1992 (Box 163, Folder 21)
  - Inter-American Labor News: Inter-American Confederation of Workers (C.I.T.), Washington, DC, circa 1970s (Box 162, Folder 24)
  - Trade Union World - Briefing: International Confederation of Free Trade Unions - ICFTU, 2002 (Box 163, Folder 49)
  - International Labor News Service: International Labor News Service, Washington, DC, 1946 (Box 163, Folder 22)
  - Wall Street by Anna Rochester: International Pamphlets - Labor Research Association, circa 1970s (Box 163, Folder 23)
  - Wage-Labour and Capital: International Publishers, New York, NY, 1933 (Box 163, Folder 24)
  - Wages and Profits in Wartime: International Publishers, New York, NY, 1941 (Box 163, Folder 25)
  - Union Record of Florida: J. Barnes, Miami, FL, 1952 (Box 163, Folder 50)
  - Labor's Voice: Labor's Voice Publishing Company, Louisville, KY, 1950 (Box 164, Folder 7)
  - Lansing Labor News: Lansing Labor News, Inc., Lansing, MI, 1954 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Proceedings: Local 1199, 1987 (Box 163, Folder 27)
  - Minnesota Labor: Minnesota State CIO Council, Minneapolis, MN, 1954 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Mon Valley Update: Mon Valley Unemployed Committee, Homestead, PA, 1990 (Box 163, Folder 28)
  - Reporter: Mon Valley Unemployed Committee, McKeesport, PA, circa 1970s (Box 163, Folder 29)
  - National Organized Labor Journal: N.O.L.J. LTD., New York, NY, 2000 (Box 167, Folder 3)
  - New Orleans News Digest: N.O.L.J. LTD., New Orleans, La, 1942 (Box 167, Folder 4)
  - National Asbestos Victims' Update: National Asbestos Victims' Legal Action Organizing Committee, circa 1970s (Box 163, Folder 30)
  - Uncommon Sense: National Jobs for All Coalition, New York, NY, circa 1970s (Box 163, Folder 31)
  - Plant Closings Bulletin: New American Movement, Chicago, IL, 1981 (Box 163, Folder 32)
  - New York City Crisis: New York Coalition to Fight Inflation & Unemployment, New York, NY, circa 1970s (Box 163, Folder 33)
  - Union Label News: New York Times Chapel, 1941 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - New York Workers' News & Perspective: New York Workers' News & Perspective, Brooklyn, NY, 1978 (Box 164, Folder 8)
  - East Coast Organizer: NYC Coalition for Jobs and Services/Baltimore and Philadelphia Strike Support Organizing Committees, New York, NY, 1972 (Box 163, Folder 34)
  - Fox Valley Labor News: Organized Labor in the Fox Valley, Aurora, IL, 1953 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Pacific Weekly: Pacific Associates, Carmel, CA, circa 1970s (Box 162, Folder 21)
  - United Labor News: Published Monthly in the Interest of the Men and Women Who Work, Canton, OH, 1981 (Box 163, Folder 1)
  - Rocky Mountain Workers' Voice: Rocky Mountain Workers' Voice, Denver, CO, circa 1970s (Box 173, Folder 19)
  - Labor-Management Relations Service Newsletter: U.S. Conference of Mayors, Washington, DC, 1980 (Box 163, Folder 36)
  - Unemployment Handbook: Unemployed Workers Organizing Committee, Portsmouth, NH, circa 1970s (Box 163, Folder 37)
  - U.W.O.C. National News: Unemployed Workers' Organizing Committee, San Leandro, CA, 1975 (Box 165, Folder 1-2)
  - Unemployed Organizer: Unemployed Workers' Organizing Committee, Chicago, IL, 1977 (Box 165, Folder 3)
  - Union Reporter: Union Reporter Association, Pennsauken, NJ, 1973-1986 (Box 165, Folder 4-6, Box 166, Folder 1-2)
  - Vermilion County Star: Vermilion County Pub. Association, Danville, IL, 1953 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Wildcat: Wildcat Press, Chicago, IL, 1969-1970 (Box 166, Folder 3)
  - Where We Stand - Labor's Road Forward: Workers Age Publishers, circa 1970s (Box 163, Folder 38)
  - Standing Up: Workers Rights Center, Minneapolis, MN, circa 1970s (Box 163, Folder 39)
  - Working Today News: Working Today, New York, NY, 1996 (Box 163, Folder 40)
  - Job Hunt News: Youth Services, New York, NY, 1940 (Box 163, Folder 41)
  - Labor News & Commentary: Nashua, NH, 1986 (Box 163, Folder 44)
  - League Bulletin Contents, 1977 (Box 163, Folder 45)
- Series IV: International Labor Organizations, 1906-2010; 6.75 Linear Feet in 6 oversize flat boxes
  This series collects various uncataloged serials and publications documenting the labor movement outside of the United States. The series contains significant quantities of material documenting unionization in Canada -- organizations include the Canadian Labour Congress; Canadian Union of Public Employees; and the Co-Operative Union of Canada -- as well as in Europe. The series also contains reports and publications issued by international bodies concerning globalization, environmental regulation, and regionally specific elements of the labor movement, specifically in Vietnam (Vietnamese Trade Unions); Japan ("Problems and Difficulties" of Japanese Workers Today: Towards the Extraction of Needs); the United Kingdom (Future of British Agriculture).
  - Class Struggle and the Strike (United States): A. Reay, Manchester, England, 1971 (Box 123, Folder 109)
  - Travail et Travailleurs en France: Acheve d'imprimer, Paris, France, 1989-1993 (Box 123, Folder 110)
  - South Africa Labor News: African-American Labor Center, 1982 (Box 123, Folder 111)
  - ASO Newsletter: Anarko-Syndikalistisk Organisation/Internationale Arbejder Association, Copenhagen, Denmark, 1989 (Box 123, Folder 112)
  - "Problems and Difficulties" of Japanese Workers Today: Towards the Extraction of Needs: Annual Reports of the Josai Graduate School Economics, Saitama, Japan, 1989 (Box 123, Folder 113)
  - Anti-Concordat: Anti-Concordat, London, England, 1979 (Box 123, Folder 114)
  - Resource Materials on Women's Labor in Japan: Asian Women Workers' Center, Saitama, Japan, 2002-2003 (Box 123, Folder 115)
  - Association of Canadian Archivists: Labor Archives Bulletin: Association of Canadian Archivists, Ottawa, Ontario, Canada, 1988-1990, 1992-1993 (Box 123, Folder 116)
  - Labor Archives Bulletin: Association of Canadian Archivists, Ottawa, Canada, 1987 (Box 123, Folder 117)
  - ASTMS Journal: Association of Scientific, Technical and Managerial Staffs, London, England, 1974 (Box 123, Folder 118)
  - Direct Action: Australian Industrial Workers of the World, Bellingen, Australia, 2001 (Box 134, Folder 1)
  - Unions are People: B.C. Federation of Labor, Vancouver, British Columbia, circa 1970s (Box 123, Folder 119)
  - Trade Unions in Britain: British Information Services, New York, NY, 1949 (Box 123, Folder 120)
  - Bulletin of the Open World Conference for the Workers International: Bulletin of the Open World Conference for the Workers International, Paris, France, 1991 (Box 123, Folder 121)
  - Cab Trade News: Cab Trade News, Ltd., London, England, 1939 (Box 123, Folder 122)
  - Cambridge Studies in Sociology: The Affluent Worker: Political Attitudes and Behaviour: Cambridge University Press, London, England, 1968 (Box 123, Folder 123)
  - Canadian Affairs: Canadian Affairs, Ottawa, Ontario, Canada, 1945 (Box 123, Folder 124)
  - Canadian Unionist: Canadian Congress of Labour, Ottawa, Canada, 1953 (Box 123, Folder 125)
  - CLC Today: Canadian Labor Congress, Ottawa, Canada, 1990-1993 (Box 134, Folder 2)
  - Social Cost of Intolerance: Canadian Labor Reports, Montreal, Canada, circa 1970s (Box 133, Folder 1)
  - Canadian Labour Congress: Canadian Labour Congress, Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada, 1961, 1962, undated (Box 133, Folder 2-3)
  - ICFTU: Canadian Labour Congress, Ottawa, Ontario, Canada, circa 1970s (Box 133, Folder 4)
  - Canadian Worker: Canadian Party of Labour, Toronto, Canada, 1972 (Box 134, Folder 6)
  - L'Ouvrier: Canadian Party of Labour, 1970 (Box 140, Folder 1)
  - CUPW Perspective: Canadian Union of Postal Workers, Ottawa, Canada, 1992-1995 (Box 134, Folder 3-5)
  - Leader: Canadian Union of Public Employees, Ottawa, Canada, circa 1970s (Box 133, Folder 18, Box 134, Folder 7)
  - Carworker: Carworker, London, England, 1973 (Box 133, Folder 5)
  - historias de la Emigracion: Centro de Documentacion de la Emigracion Espanola, Madrid, Spain, 2005 (Box 133, Folder 6)
  - Charter: Charter, London, England, circa 1970s (Box 133, Folder 7)
  - China Labour Bulletin: China Labour Bulletin, Kowloon, Hong Kong, 1994-1996, 1999, 2000 (Box 133, Folder 8)
  - CFL News: Chinese Federation of Labor, Taipei, Taiwan, 1986, 1988 (Box 133, Folder 9)
  - Various publications: Chinese Staff & Workers' Association, New york, NY, 1995 (Box 133, Folder 10)
  - CSWA News: Chinese Staff Workers' Association, New York, NY, 1993-1994 (Box 133, Folder 11)
  - Espoir: CNT-AIT, Spain, 1977, 1979-1982 (Box 135, Folder 1-8, Box 136, Folder 1-3)
  - Collier: Collier, South Yorkshire, England, 1977-1978 (Box 133, Folder 13)
  - Loita Obreira: Comisiones Obreras de La Coruna, 1974 (Box 133, Folder 14)
  - La Commune: Comite de Liaison et d'Action pour la Democratie Ouvriere, Paris, France, 1957-1958, 1971, undated (Box 133, Folder 15)
  - Fragua Social: Confederacion Nacional del Trabajo del Pais Valencia, Barcelona, Spain, 1978 (Box 133, Folder 16)
  - Nouvelles CSN: Confederation des Syndicats Nationaux, Montreal, Canada, 1993 (Box 133, Folder 17)
  - XXXIIIe Congres National Corporatif de Paris: Confederation Generale du Travail Force Ouvriere, Paris, France, 1948 (Box 133, Folder 19)
  - FNV News: Confederation Netherlands Trade Union Movement (FNV), Amsterdam, Netherlands, 1977 (Box 133, Folder 20)
  - Canadian Co-operator: A Magazine of Social and Economic Progress: Co-operative Union of Canada, Brantford, Canada, 1938 (Box 133, Folder 12)
  - La Estiba: Voz de los Puertos: Boletin de la Coordinadora Estatal de los Estibadores Portuarios: Coordinadora Estatal de los Estibadores Portuarios, Barcelona, Spain, 1988-1991 (Box 136, Folder 5-7)
  - Feinde der Demokratie: Presseschau und Kommentare aus Gewekschaftlicher Sicht Jnformationen: Deutschen GewerkSchaftsbundes, Hanover, Germany, 1959 (Box 133, Folder 21)
  - Der Urbeitgeber: Deutschen Urbeitgeberverbande, 1928 (Box 133, Folder 22)
  - Dockworker: Dockworker, London, England, 1973 (Box 133, Folder 23)
  - Rank and File Contact: Electrical, Electronic, Telecommunications and Plumbing Union (EETPU), London, England, 1978 (Box 172, Folder 50)
  - ELF: European Labour Forum, Nottingham, England, 1991 (Box 133, Folder 24)
  - Pfingstkongress der FAU/IAA: FAU/IAA, Dessau, Germany, 1998 (Box 133, Folder 27)
  - Metall Info Brief: FAU-IAA (Freie ArbeiterInnen Union-Internationale Arbeiter Assoziation), Germany, 1989 (Box 133, Folder 25)
  - Gisdatigo: FAU-IWA, Berlin, Germany, 1997 (Box 133, Folder 26)
  - Butlleti Informatiu de la Federacio Sindical Textil "Radium": Federacio Sindical Textil "Radium", Barcelona, Spain, 1995, 1999-2004 (Box 133, Folder 28)
  - La Union del Marino: Federacion Obrera Maritima, Buenos Aires, Argentina, 1925 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Orientaciones: órgano de la Federación Regional de Sindicatos de la Enseñanza del Centro: Federación Regional de Sindicatos de la Enseñanza del Centro, Madrid, Spain, 1937 (Box 136, Folder 4)
  - Unity: Federated Workers' Union of Ireland, Dublin, Republic of Ireland, 1985 (Box 133, Folder 30)
  - Le Monde Ouvrier/The Labor World: Federation du Travail du Quebec, Montreal, Canada, 1953 (Box 133, Folder 31)